springrole.com 2017-05-16

# SpringRole- Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

SpringRole Inc. (“SpringRole”, "Company", "we" or "us") provides the user and/or viewer ("you") with access to information through this website (the "Site") and provides certain products and services in conjunction with this Site (the “Services”). This privacy policy describes our information collection and use practices in connection with the Site and the Services, as well as circumstances under which we disclose information collected from you. 

Information

"Personal Information" means data that allows someone to identify or contact you (e.g. your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit/debit numbers, expiration date and other billing information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number). "Non-Personal Information" means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information. 

how information is obtained

Information That Is Gathered From Visitors

In common with other websites, log files are stored on our web server saving details such as the visitor's Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session) address, browser type, referring page and time of visit. Such information is not associated with any online account or registration information. 

Information You Give Us

We receive and store information that you enter on the Site or give us in any other way (e.g., by telephone). This may include information you provide when you engage in transactions, search, contact customer service, or participate in contests, promotions, surveys, forums, content submissions, chats, bulletin boards, discussion groups, requests for suggestions or other aspects or services offered by us. As a result, you may supply us with such Personal Information. By submitting Personal Information through the Site or the Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized alteration of Personal Information in Company's possession and control. Although we endeavor to provide security for information in our possession and control, no security system can prevent against all potential security breaches, and we bear no liability for uses or disclosures of Personal Information or Non-Personal Information arising in connection with the theft thereof. 

How the Information is Used

We use information collected from our Site and the Services in several ways. For example, we use Personal Information as needed to provide the Site and the Services. We may send E-mails to you regarding news of the Services or offers by us or our affiliates. We also use both Personal Information and Non-Personal Information when evaluating ways to improve the Site and the Services. As further described below, in limited circumstances we may disclose collected information, including Personal Information, to certain third parties in connection with providing the Services or as required by law. We use Non-Personal Information in a variety of ways, including, by way of example, to evaluate the performance of the Site and Services and the general preferences of users, or to generate anonymous statistics for our benefit or for our business partners. Because Non-Personal Information is entirely anonymous, and therefore can never be used by us to identify you, this policy does not limit our ability to use or disclose Non-Personal Information. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you enter and win a contest or other promotion, you expressly consent to us (a) providing your Personal Information (e.g., your name and address) to the third party providing the prize for the contest or other promotion, solely to provide you such prize and (b) publicly disclosing your name and the fact that you won the contest or promotion. 

Information Shared with Third Parties

In addition, as a necessary part of providing the Services, we may disclose information collected from you to certain third parties. For example, we may disclose certain Personal Information about you to our third-party service providers (e.g., our third party payment processors), so long as they are only using the Personal Information to provide services to us. If another company acquires our company, business, or our assets, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by it and us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. Under certain limited circumstances, we may cooperate with legal investigations and/or we may be subject to legal requirements to disclose information collected through the Site or the Services, such as, by way of example, to a court or a governmental agency, and our policy is to provide such cooperation and comply fully with all such legal requirements. We may also disclose Personal Information to protect or defend the rights or property of Company or users of the Services and/or to investigate any violation or potential violation of the law, this Privacy Policy, or the Terms and Conditions. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. The disclosures contemplated by this paragraph (“Necessary Disclosures”) are necessary if you wish to use the Services. As mentioned above, Company may use and disclose Non-Personal Information without restriction. If you do not want us to make such Necessary Disclosures, or to use Non-Personal Information without restriction, you must not use the Services. We do not sell, rent or lease e-mail addresses to third parties. 

Visitor Options

If you have subscribed to one or more of our Services, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions which are included in the e-mail that you receive. 

Cookies

Cookies are small digital signature files that are stored by your web browser that allow your preferences to be recorded when visiting the Site. They may also be used to track your return visits to the Site. When using the Services, we may create “cookies” on your computer for purposes of facilitating and maintaining your current user session, and may collect Personal Information using those cookies in order to enable Company to identify you in connection with the Services and to track use of the Services for purposes consistent with this policy. To make our Site and Services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, IP, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. Third party advertising companies may also use cookies for tracking purposes. You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings, but this may prevent you from access to certain features of the website. 

Minors

You must be of age 18 or older to place orders with the Company. 

Changes to Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the Site so that users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we will disclose it. These changes will be effective immediately. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. Your continued access to and/or use of the Site or the Services following notice of such changes constitutes your assent to, and acceptance of, this policy, including all posted changes for which we have provided notice as described herein. 

Questions

For any questions or comments on our privacy policy please contact us at [privacy@springrole.com](mailto:privacy@springrole.com)
